ustvnow.com 2018-06-27

# USTVnow Privacy Policy – USTVnow Support

Privacy Policy

 USTVNOW Privacy Policy

Last updated: July 17, 2012

This Privacy Policy provides important information about your privacy in connection with your use of DutchPhone Holdings Inc. DBA USTVNOW. Please review it carefully. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in our Terms of Use. By accessing or using USTVNOW including, without limitation, the USTVNOW web site(s), USTVNOW Equipment and/or USTVNOW Platform (hereafter "USTVNOW"), you consent to this Privacy Policy and the practices set forth herein, as well as our.

 Our Commitment to Privacy

At USTVNOW, we take your privacy very seriously. We are committed to complying with all applicable federal, state and local privacy laws and regulations. We strive to provide an environment in which our customers trust us to handle personal information responsibly. We provide this privacy notice as part of our commitment to privacy by describing the personal information that we collect, how we use it, how we protect it, and with whom we share it.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use your information, including personally identifiable data, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, internet protocol address and payment and/or credit card information (collectively, "Personal Data"), as well as certain other information including, without limitation, demographic and usage information (collectively "Other Data"). Such Personal Data and Other Data may be collected from and about, or with respect to, USTVNOW Members and/or users of: a) any USTVNOW website, including the current site at USTVNOW.com, b) USTVNOW Equipment and/or c) the USTVNOW Platform ("USTVNOW Users"). This Privacy Policy applies to all USTVNOW Members and/or USTVNOW Users.

 Information That We Collect

When you register to become an USTVNOW Member and/or become an USTVNOW User, we may collect the following data from you:

Personal Data: We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you register to become an USTVNOW Member, become an USTVNOW User and/or contact us with inquiries that may contain such data. Other Data: We also collect Other Data, including the Research Data described below, about your use of USTVNOW and about your Supported Devices and/or other devices or browsers through which you may access USTVNOW. In addition, as set forth in more detail below, we may obtain, collect and store demographic information, such as gender, age, occupation, hobbies and interests or similar information. We may receive information about you from other sources including third party sources, online or offline, and add it to the information that you provided to us and/or that we collected. We may also receive other data or information from or through you about third parties, such as a third party email address in connection with the "invite a friend" feature, if you provide such information directly or enable USTVNOW to access that information maintained in a third party resource such as, for one example, your email provider. We may use such data to contact that third party with respect to your use of the "invite a friend" feature as well as for other USTVNOW related marketing.

Cookies and Web Beacons: When you visit the USTVNOW web site or interact with USTVNOW, we receive and store certain information. Such information is collected passively using various technologies like web beacons and may be used to track usage of USTVNOW and/or to customize and improve USTVNOW including the USTVNOW Equipment and/or the USTVNOW Platform, improve the quality of our products and/or service to you or in connection with marketing USTVNOW. In operating USTVNOW we may also use standard technologies, including "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer which hosts the USTVNOW website gives to your browser when you access the USTVNOW website. Our cookies help provide additional and improved functionality and help us to analyze USTVNOW usage. For instance, the USTVNOW website may set a cookie on your browser that may allow you to elect to utilize your USTVNOW Membership without needing to remember and then enter a password.

Log information: When you access USTVNOW via a browser, application or other client, our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with USTVNOW, your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

Research Data and Aggregated Data: In an ongoing effort to improve USTVNOW, USTVNOW may conduct research and obtain data, either directly or through or from third parties (e.g. Google Analytics), on its individual customers' demographics, interests and behavior based on Personal Data and Other Data that USTVNOW will provide such third party and USTVNOW will maintain and use data ("Research Data") resulting from and/or connected to that research. In addition, USTVNOW and/or a third party may compile Personal Data and/or Other Data on an aggregated basis ("Aggregate Data"). USTVNOW may share this Aggregate Data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This Aggregate Data does not identify you personally.

 Additional Information About Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Data

If you provide Personal Data for a certain purpose, we may use the Personal Data for that purpose. For example, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to USTVNOW, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to USTVNOW. We may also use your Personal Data to monitor your use of USTVNOW and to contact you regarding your use of USTVNOW. In addition, USTVNOW or its authorized service providers, may use financial information or payment methods, such as credit cards, to process payment for any purchases made through USTVNOW, to protect against fraudulent transactions and otherwise as needed to monitor and manage our business. USTVNOW may use your Personal Data and Other Data, including Research Data, collected to help us improve the functionality of USTVNOW, to better understand our users, to personalize USTVNOW and to improve USTVNOW. USTVNOW may use your residential address, your Internet protocol address and other technical measures, including geo-location, to verify your location.

We may also use information that you have provided to us to contact you in the future to tell you about products and functionality that we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each email we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future emails. If at any time you wish not to receive any future emails or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

 Children

While USTVNOW provides USTVNOW Equipment and/or the USTVNOW Platform by which Members may choose to access broadcast television and other content, our Terms of Use expressly prohibit anyone under eighteen (18) from registering for an USTVNOW Membership and require that any use of an USTVNOW Membership by a family member under the age of eighteen (18) be under the direct supervision of their parent or guardian. We do not intentionally seek to collect Personal Data from children under the age of thirteen (13), nor do we knowingly collect Personal Data from children younger than thirteen (13). If you are under the age of thirteen (13), you are not permitted to submit, and please do not submit, any Personal Data through USTVNOW and/or in connection with any Member account. If you think that a child under the age of thirteen (13) has provided Personal Data to USTVNOW, please contact us and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

 Our Disclosure of Your Data

There are certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data and/or Other Data with certain third parties without further notice to you:

Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we might sell, buy or merge businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data and/or Other Data may be part of the transferred assets.

Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: USTVNOW, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies and/or consultants to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include credit card and other payment processing, testing our products and/or researching and analyzing user demographics and behavior. In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your Personal Data and/or Other Data.

Legal Requirements: USTVNOW may disclose your Personal Data and/or Other Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation or a government request, (ii) verify compliance with or enforce our Terms of Use or protect and defend the rights or property of USTVNOW, USTVNOW Users or others (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of USTVNOW Members, USTVNOW Users or the public and/or (iv) protect against legal liability.

Third Party Services: USTVNOW allows you to enable and/or or log in via various online third party services, such as social media and social networking services like Facebook or Twitter and email providers such as Google or Yahoo ("Third Party Services") and allows some aspects of those services to be integrated into the USTVNOW Platform. For example, if you log in to USTVNOW using a social networking service, information that you share via that service may be reflected on the USTVNOW Platform. Likewise, if you enable USTVNOW to have access to an email contact through a Third Party Service, USTVNOW may use that data to send an invitation or market to that contact.

When you log into or use USTVNOW using your Third Party Services account, we will collect and share relevant information necessary to enable the USTVNOW website or account to access that Third Party Service and your data contained within that Third Party Service. The Third Party Service may collect information as well. Please remember that the manner in which a Third Party Service collects, stores and discloses your information is governed solely by the policies of that Third Party Service and USTVNOW will have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices, terms of use and/or other actions of any third party site or service that you may enable.

 Exclusions

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Data that is intentionally collected by USTVNOW through and/or in connection with USTVNOW's website, Equipment and/or Platform. This Privacy Policy will not apply to any additional unsolicited information that you choose to provide to USTVNOW through this website or through any other means, including any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). USTVNOW has no obligation with respect to such unsolicited information and will be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

The USTVNOW Platform may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by USTVNOW ("Third Party Sites"). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

 Security -How We Protect Your Information

USTVNOW takes reasonable steps including physical, electronic and procedural measures to safeguard the Personal Data in our possession against loss, misuse, theft, and unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification.

However, no Internet or email transmission or electronic storage of information is ever completely secure or error free. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. You should take special care in deciding what information you send via USTVNOW. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data and/or Other Data to USTVNOW or utilizing any social networking features in connection with USTVNOW.

 Changes and Updates

USTVNOW, our business and the law may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for USTVNOW to make changes to this Privacy Policy. USTVNOW RESERVES THE RIGHT TO PERIODICALLY UPDATE OR MODIFY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE TO YOU. PLEASE REVIEW THE PRIVACY POLICY PERIODICALLY, AND ESPECIALLY BEFORE YOU PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL DATA. THIS PRIVACY POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED ON THE DATE INDICATED ABOVE AND YOUR CONTINUED USE OF USTVNOW AFTER ANY CHANGES OR REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY INDICATES YOUR AGREEMENT WITH THE REVISED TERMS. THE MOST CURRENT VERSION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAN BE REVIEWED BY VISITING THE USTVNOW WEBSITE AND CLICKING ON THE "PRIVACY POLICY" LINK. THE MOST CURRENT VERSION OF THE PRIVACY POLICY WILL SUPERSEDE ALL PREVIOUS VERSIONS.

 Contact Us

If you are a Member, you may keep your Personal Data accurate and current by logging into your account and updating your information. You also may choose to close your account at any time. After you close your account, you will not be able to sign in to your account or access any of your information, although we may still retain certain information associated with your account.

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions about USTVNOW's Privacy Policy or USTVNOW's information practices. We welcome your feedback!

DutchPhone Holdings, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
28 West 27 Street Floor 2

New York, NY 10001

care@ustvnow.com
